I lost 2 lbs last week while eating an
entire pint of ice cream every single
night. I mean, it's pretty easy when you
can use your Ninja Creamy to recreate
your favorite ice cream flavors, but way
lower in calories and much higher in
protein. Here are the seven pints I made
this week. That first pint you saw was a
peanut butter Oreo flavor, which is a
peanut butter base with Oreos mixed in.
Now, this is a Ben & Jerry's recreation
of their flavor, Impressively Fudge,
which is chocolate ice cream with
chocolate covered pretzels mixed in.
Then I did the new Dairy Queen Blizzard,
which is pumpkin pie, which was a
pumpkin spice base with pie pieces mixed
in. Now this is a maple creamy, kind of
like maple soft serve, kind of like
maple ice cream, a nice cross in
between. Then I recreated yet another
Ben & Jerry's flavor. This is one love,
which is a banana ice cream with a
chocolate chip swirl, and then caramel
and graham cracker on top. Then I did
some strawberry soft serve because
everyone was asking for this, and the
recipe is actually super simple. And
finally, I was in Maine on a family
vacation. I brought a Ninja Creamy and I
made them cookie dough ice cream and
salted caramel brownie ice cream. Of
course, both packed with protein and low
in